ABOUT ME

A small introduction about myself



Ryan Conabeare

English National. Living & Working in Patagonia Since 2008

Growing up in Devon in the UK nature has always been by my side. With Dartmoor and Exmoor as our backdrop my family spent most weekends Hiking, Fishing and Surfing on the north Devon Coast.

In 2006 I moved to the Americas, Working and living several years in Colorado and eventually heading south and making Patagonia my Home.

SKILLS & EXPERTISE

Twenty years of professional Experience including Tourism, Hospitality, IT and Construction.

Enthusiastic, Hardworking and experienced in a varied array of activities. Since finishing my studies I have continuously worked in different professions including Construction, IT, Tourism and Hospitality. In 2012 I built my family home and as a side project am currently building rental properties. My interests include Snowboarding, Fishing, Hiking, Music, Reading, Swimming, Outdoors activities and Computing.

WORK EXPERIENCE

My previous associations

CARPENTERIA GIAI Carpentry and Joinery 2015 - 2022

Working with one of Argentina's finest joinery outfits. I have designed, built and installed unique furniture for Local, National and International clients.

PIEDRAS BLANCAS BARILOCHE Team Manager 2012 - 2015

Working directly with international tourists in this local ski and winter activity destination. I was responsible for overseeing the day to day operations which included Ski Rental, Restaurant Stock and General Maintenance to ensure that customer service standards were maintained.

BARILOCHE WIRELESS SRL Network Engineer 2009 - 2012

Working in Bariloche and the surrounding area. Developing and maintaining a Wide Area Network for a Local Internet Service Provider. This Job required professional IT skills, Electrical installation knowledge and regular customer interaction.

WESTERN UNION Technical Support Agent 2008 - 2009

Working from Buenos Aires to offer technical support for thousands of US based Western Union locations. This project required an extensive knowledge of Western Unions proprietary Money

Transfer Software and Hardware. The project required effective communication Skills to understand and interpret customer issues and provide them with step by step solutions in a timely manner.

VAIL RESORTS Wildwood Restaurant 2006 - 2008

Working 'on mountain' for Vail mountain dining, this job required an array of skills. Working with a large and diverse team my responsibilities included Stock Management, Cooking and Cleaning and Client end Services.

DAVE WRIGHT ELECTRICAL LTD Electrical Technician 2000 - 2006

Professional Electrical Installation for Domestic, Commercial and Industrial projects Locally and Nationally. Managing, coordinating and implementing installations for several large developers. Working and coordinating across management to apprenticeships.

EDUCATION & DIPLOMAS

EAST DEVON COLLEGE

NVQ Level 3 in Electrical Engineering

BTEC Key skills Level 2 in Application of Number, Communication and I.T

City and Guilds NVQ Level 3 Qualifications for Electrical Engineering

City and Guilds NVQ Level 3 and Joint Industry Board for the Electrical Contracting Industry

Installing and Commissioning Electro Technical Systems

National Electro Technical Training Organization – AM2 Practical Skills Test

TIVERTON HIGH SCHOOL

GCSE

B grade average in English, Geography, Mathematics, Graphic Design, Science, I.T, Art and design, German.

GET IN TOUCH

WhatsApp me at +541130806425

DROP ME AN EMAIL

Contact me at ryanconabeare@gmail.com